Contact

tejaskochar321@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tejaskochar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

С

Web Development

C++

Languages

Marwari (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Marathi (Limited Working)

Certifications

Machine Learning A-Z: Hands-On Python & R In Data Science

Tejas Kochar

Final Year CS Undergrad @NITRR || Backend Developer || Machine Learning Enthusiast

Raipur

Summary

Experienced Developer Skilled in Data Structures, Competitive Programming, Operating System, Database Management, Web development, Django Developer, Machine Learning Enthusiast. Strong Engineering professional with Bachelor of Technology focused in Computer Science from National Institute of Technology, Raipur.

Experience

Dalalstreet.ai Artificial Intelligence Intern June 2020 - August 2020 (3 months) India

We focused on applying data science to develop investment signals in financial market.

I developed a web scraping tool using beautifulsoup, spacy and requests for news analysis on 16+ Media websites. Also, pre-trained on news corpuses and applied NLP on scraped financial news data to predict a sentiment score.

Public & Media Relations Cell, NIT Raipur 1 year 11 months

Core Coordinator
June 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Manager September 2018 - May 2019 (9 months)

Literary Committee Coordinator October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months) NIT Raipur

Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur B.Tech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Hislop College, Temple Road, Civil Lines, Nagpur 12th · (2015 - 2017)